混乱之子 前情提要
Previously on Sons of Anarchy...
算是给Cacuzza慈善基金的捐款
Donation for the Cacuzza charity fund.
还有一箱克罗格手枪给你 以备不时之需
And a case of Glocks for your trouble.
嗯 很不错
Yeah, that works.
你和Lowen在搞什么鬼？
What are you doing with Lowen?!
你要和Jax离婚？
You divorcing Jax?
你打算在监护人的事情上造反吗？
You planning on some kind of custody coup?!
我对我家人做什么不关你的事
What I do with my family is none of your business.
婊子
Bitch!
老天
Jesus!
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
我肚里的孩子...
My baby...
瞧你干的好事
Look what you did.
不是我干的
I didn't do that.
是的 就是你 我们都亲眼目睹
Yes, you did.We all saw it.
我再也不想让她接近我们的孩子
I don't ever want her near our children again.
答应我
Promise me.
我答应
I promise.
你再也看不到孩子们了
You will never see those kids again.
他们的奶奶已经死了
Grandma is dead.
你很清楚 该进监狱不是你
You know it's not you who deserves to be in jail.
举证非法的枪支交易 就可以得到完全的豁免
Full immunity for the proof of the gun running.
这是你唯一能得到的条件
It's the only offer you'll get.
我不需要考虑你的条件
I don't need to think about an offer.
我来和你谈谈价码
I'm here to make you an offer.
Gaalan O'Shay 我会把他交给你 附赠一船的枪支 绝不拖泥带水
Gaalan O'Shay-- I will deliver him with
a shipment of guns, open and shut.
你想的到什么好处？
What's in it for you?
豁免俱乐部一切关于枪支的指控 包括过去和现在的
Immunity for the MC for all gun charges past and present.
我估计你还有个人的打算吧
I figureyou also have a personal request.
你必须重新审视一下Tara的案子
You need to look at Tara's case again.
我觉得你应该回头想想 从另一个角度看看发生的事情
I think that you should go back,
take another look at what happened.
从中找出真相
Find the truth in all of it.
你觉得我的老婆在撒谎
You think my wife is a liar?
住手 住手
Stop it! Stop it!
亲爱的 这一切都是谎言 包括怀孕和流产
Honey, it was all a lie, the pregnancy the miscarriage.
Tara想一走了之 离开你 离开帮会
Tara wants out, Jax, from you, the club.
这就是真相
This is the truth.
要是她不肯告诉你 你就得找个愿意告诉你的人
And if she won't tell you, you need to find someone who will.
Tara打算和我离婚？
Is Tara divorcing me?
是的
Yes.
还要带走我的孩子？
And taking my sons.
滚出去
Get out!
Tara 是我 Ally Lowen
Tara, it's Ally Lowen.
Thomas?
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
Abel!
你应该让他再睡一会
You should let him sleep.
嘿 宝贝
Hi, sweetie.
会有人看着你
There'll be someone watching you.
别试图把他们带走
Don't try to take them anywhere.
你打算怎么办？
What are you gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
很多事情 我现在看不透
I can't see anything right now.
但是假如我们不保持一些距离 会有人受到伤害的
But if I don't put some distance
here, someone's gonna get hurt.
你的辩护律师怎么说？
Your lawyer say why?
估计是法官要优先处理
Guess the judge wants to get out ahead of all
都是该死的媒体 都盯着帮会的事
the bad press been falling on my club.
要拉拢陪审团 又要人不知道 这可不容易 老兄
Ain't easy pulling a jury that
ain't been exposed to all that shit, man.
是啊 我知道
- Yeah, I know.
哎 老兄
- Whew. Man.
到底怎么了？
What the hell happened?
给我穿了双倍的束身衣 还把我交给得罪过的看守
Shrink double-dipped, gave me to the guard I went off on.
怎么又把你弄回普通囚房？
How'd you land back in gen pop?
他们把我拖出去 和我的律师谈了
They yanked me out to have a chat with my lawyer.
我的庭审时间被提前了
My trial's been moved up.
嗯 他们明天就要用囚车把我转移到郡里
Yeah, they cart me off to county tomorrow.
糟糕
Shit.
这就麻烦了
That's a problem.
是啊
Yes, it is.
你转告Gaalan 叫他联络Jax
You tell Gaalan.You have him reach out to Jax.
你打了那些业务电话吗？
You able make to those business calls?
打了 一切正常
Yeah, it's all in play.
还有 呃 让我的律师把我太太叫过来
And, uh, had my lawyer get my old lady down here.
我要处理一些私人事务
I'll take care of all my personal shit.
你要告诉Gaalan 明天务必要行动 明白吗？
But you tell Gaalan he has got to
make this happen tomorrow, all right?
这非常关键
Pope was capital.
要是我得到有罪判决 鬼知道他们会把我送到哪
That guilty verdict can send me anywhere.
那么 一切事情都告吹
And then all this goes away.
我会转告的
I'll pass it along.
孤独地骑行在这尘世
Riding through this world all alone
上帝将灵魂带走
God takes your soul
徒剩躯壳
You're on your own
如乌鸦掠过天际
The crow flies straight
直飞远方
a perfect line
缠绵在恶魔之床
on the devil's bed
直至死亡
until you die
才将这一世轨迹
Gotta look this life
看个端详
in the eye
混乱之子 第六季 第十集
英语字幕：n17t01 翻译：Wilsonyy 校对：Dena
哪位？
Yes?
是我 Margaret
It's Margaret.
嗨
Hi.
我看见孩子们在日托所 估计你会在这
I saw the boys were in
daycare, was hoping you might be here.
是啊
Yeah.
正在看...
Just looking at...
律师的简历
lawyer résumés.
为什么？怎么了？
Why? What happened?
Jax都知道了
Jax knows the truth.
他威胁Lowen 于是她....把一切都告诉了他
He threatened Lowen, and she...told him everything.
他干什么了？
What did he do?
哦 他没有伤害她
Oh, he didn't hurt her.
也没对我动手
Me, either.
我不知道 是什么原因让他去逼迫Lowen
And I don't know what pushed him at Lowen.
肯定是Gemma
Gemma.
昨天她来过这
She came here yesterday.
说她知道我伪造文件来帮你
Said she knew I forged documents to help you.
威胁说要捅到医院董事会
Threatened to tell the hospital.
她是在虚张声势 但是我反应 呃 有点太傲慢了
She was bluffing, but my
response was, uh, too cavalier.
我...她知道我在保护你
I... She knew I was protecting you.
发生什么事情？
What happened?
我告诉她 她没办法证明什么
I told her she couldn't prove anything.
她说她不会去证实 但是她儿子会
She said she didn't have to, that her son would.
她只是需要一个比瘾君子更可靠的消息来源
She just needed a more reliable source than a junkie.
Wendy肯定说了
Wendy must have talked.
昨晚我很害怕回家 Tara
I was afraid to go home last night, Tara.
我告诉Dave我得通宵加班
I told Dave that I had to work through the night.
于是我....一直待在这 我知道这里有保安
And I... I stayed here, where I knew there were guards.
不 不 Jax是通过Lowen知道的
No, no, Jax-Jax got his information from Lowen.
我肯定他不会骚扰你
I really doubt he'd bother you.
我不能冒这个险
I can't take that chance.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
呃 我要休三个星期的假
Um, I've got three weeks of vacation and comp time,
我会把家里人带上
and I'm gonna take 'em.
到Sedosa我姐姐家
I'm gonna go stay with my sister in Sedona.
我明白了
I understand.
真对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你自己一定要小心
Please be careful.
嘿
Hey.
不知道你能不能对付
Wasn't sure if you'd make it.
我来了
I'm here.
今天早上到的
Showed up this morning.
Diosa Del Sur三陪按摩中心 正式开张了
Diosa Del Sur Escorts and
Massage, officially in business.
啊 太棒了
Ah, that's great.
是的
Yes, it is.
谢谢你们 先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.
我不清楚发生了什么事 但是别再调皮了
I'm not sure what happened, but no more fighting.
我让Lyla过来和姑娘们谈谈 看看她们的资料
I'll have Lyla come sit down
with the girls. Get their info.
确保每一位都按规定缴税
Make sure we have everyone's W-9s.
够不上Diosa档次的 一律清除出革命队伍
Weed out anyone who's not
up to Diosa's very high standards.
就这么办
Something like that.
你 呃 需要我帮你把东西放到哪儿吗 亲爱的？
You, um, you want me to put this someplace, sweetie?
不 我自己来 亲爱的 谢谢
No. I got it, darling.Thank you.
不介意的话 我想在这对付几晚
Just gonna crash here for a few
nights, if you don't mind.
当然不介意
Of course not.
来吧
Come on.
暂时把你的东西放到我的房间
Put your stuff in my room for now.
感激不尽
Appreciate that.
什么原因让你不在家里住？
Any reason why you're not sleeping at home?
呃 你不会想知道的
Uh, you don't wanna know.
由你吧
You're probably right.
嘿
Hey.
怎么了？
What's going on?
是关于Clay的事情
I got a Clay thing.
我们还有 关于爱尔兰人的事
We've got an Irish thing.
用我的办公室吧
Use my office.
我是Gemma Teller
Gemma Teller.
我是Colette Jane 幸会
Colette Jane.Pleasure.
久仰大名
That's what I hear.
Clay想要见我
Clay wants to see me.
他的律师说 他下午过来接我
Lawyer says he can get me in this afternoon.
他有没有说什么原因？
Did he say why?
他想签署一些文件
Papers he wants signed.
就是这一类的事情
Something like that.
也许他只是想找个见面的借口
It's probably just an excuse for a sit-down.
爱尔兰人那边又是怎么回事？
What's going on with the Irish?
没事 大多数事情他都很清楚
It's okay. He knows most of it.
好吧 Gaalan来了
Okay.Gaalan's in town.
说要我们去碰个面
Says we have to see him.
Nor-u-Bev 饮料仓库 20分钟之后
Nor-u-Bev, 20 minutes.
你认为会是什么事情？
Got any idea what it might be?
不清楚
No.
我们应该马上出发 一会桥上会很塞车
We should get going, the bridge is gonna be jammed.
我有些事情想告诉你和Nero
I got something I need to tell you and Nero.
需要我们回避吗？
You want us to split?
不用
No.
我要你们也听听
I want you to hear this, too.
昨晚我和Lowen谈过
I talked to Lowen last night.
了解到了一些真相 关于Tara的事情
I got some truth about what happened with Tara.
她根本没有怀孕
She was never pregnant.
Tara算计我老妈....
Tara set up my mom...
让它看上去是流产了
made it look like a miscarriage
这样就能让我签字同意 不让Gemma成为我儿子的法定监护人
so that I would sign off on Gemma never
becoming legal guardian of our sons.
她想和我离婚
She wants to divorce me.
她想争取到完全监护权 还想一走了之
She wants full custody, and she was gonna split.
老天
Jesus.
要是她进监狱怎么办？
What about jail?
假如她真的要服刑 她要确保
Well, if she served time,she was gonna make sure
Wendy成为监护人 并且要她把孩子们从Charming镇带走
Wendy became guardian and that she got my sons out of Charming.
对不起 我没有相信你的话
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
你怎么可以这样？
How could you?
我很难过 亲爱的
I'm so sorry, honey.
对不起 老兄
Sorry, man.
我理解 兄弟
I know, mano.
没事的
It's okay.
你打算怎么办 兄弟？
What do you want to do, brother?
眼下 我让West看着Tara...
I got West watching Tara right now...
确保她不会乱跑
making sure she doesn't go anywhere.
我现在实在是有点想不通
None of this makes sense to me right now.
我想我需要一些时间 想想解决的办法
I just think I need a couple days, figure it out.
她不认识West
She doesn't know West.
也许叫一个熟面孔跟着她会更好些
Might be better if she had a familiar face behind her.
让她只在家附近转悠
Keep her motivated to stay close to home.
我去看着她吧
I can watch her.
嗯 好吧 谢谢
Yeah, okay. Thanks.
我们都站在你一边 兄弟
We're here, man.
有什么需要尽管开口
Let us know if you need anything.
好了 我们走吧
All right, let's get out of here.
你应付这里？
You handle this?
是的 这里有我
Yeah, I got it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
与Clay小心点
Be careful with Clay.
我没事
I'll be fine.
当心那个贝尔法斯特屠夫
Be careful with the butcher of Belfast.
我们会尽量保证安全
We'll try to stay in one piece.
回头见
I'll see you later.
嗯 回见
Yeah, you will.
他陷进去多久了？
How long has he been dipping into that?
不太久
Not long.
嘿 他只不过解决妈咪问题
Hey, he's working out his mommy issues.
那么你呢 皮条老爹？
How 'bout you, pimp daddy?
你也想解决某个妈咪问题？
You want to work out some mommy issues?
嘿 这就是为什么我和你在一起的原因
Hey, that's why I'm with you, mama.
我可要打你那性感的小屁股
I may spank that brown ass.
小心点
Be careful.
估计能搞定 完了以后我们再谈
Consider it handled. We'll talk when it's done.
他们来了
They're here now.
Jackson.
谢谢你啊 这么快就赶过来了
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
嗯 什么事情这么重要？
Yeah. So what's so important?
时间紧迫 小伙子
It's all about the timing, son.
听说Clay都打过电话了
Heard Clay made his calls.
是的 每个买家都搞定了 除了那帮意大利佬
Yeah, everyone's locked down except the Italians.
Cacuzza 还在犹豫不决
Cacuzza's undecided.
那可是你的大客户
That's your biggest customer.
三个大家族 两大块地盘
Three families, two territories.
我知道
I know.
他正在权衡中国佬的价码
He's weighing an offer from the Chinese.
我还以为Jimmy是Clay的忠诚客户
I thought Jimmy was loyal to Clay?
他是的
He is.
他只是想让我们为他们的生意着急上火
He's just trying to make us do
a little dance for their business.
你们什么时候谈判？
So when do you talk?
这儿完了我们就去
We're on our way from here.
Cacuzza先见我们 然后才见林氏家族
Cacuzza's meeting with us
first, then the Lin family.
我认为我们应该给他展示一些新产品
I figured we'd show him some of the new mods.
已经准备好了
Already assembled.
我们带了9箱AK冲锋枪
Got nine cases of the AK's
配备新型瞄准器和枪托
with the new scopes and grips.
我们可以把这些新货带上 帮助你们达成交易
We can bring 'em to the meet,help you close the deal.
很好 我会搞定Cacuzza
That's okay. I'll get Cacuzza on board.
肯定的 但你必须带上Conor一起去
No doubt. But just take Connor.
为了表示敬意 让他们知道 我们有多重视与他们的生意
Shows respect, lets them know how
much we value their business.
有道理的
Makes sense.
我会让你做主
I'll let you run it.
没时间扯皮了 小伙子
No time for discussion, son.
我们必须今天就把生意谈下来
We need to close the deal today.
为什么这么着急？
What's the big rush?
为什么我会这样要求
Why I asked you here.
是因为Clay的庭审提前了
Clay's trial has been moved up.
他们明天就会把他转送出去
They transport him tomorrow.
哦 糟了
Aw, shit.
是啊 我们的计划有麻烦了
Aye. It complicates our plan.
我们需要一些帮助
Gonna need some help.
我们不会参与劫持囚车
We're not part of taking down that transport.
我们准备好撤退的车辆、路线和行动计划
I have the vehicles, the route, the plan.
不费吹灰之力
It'll happen without a hitch.
我的人来不及赶过来
I can't get a crew here in time.
我需要你们6个人做帮手
Need about six of your men.
要是我说“不”呢？
And what if we say no?
你真的不可以这样 Jackson
You really can't, Jackson.
把这个建议交到你们的议事堂 投票表决吧
Take it to your table, have one of your votes.
我们彼此都需要这事能成
But we both need this to happen.
让我们的枪支生意继续推进 让你们全身而退
Moves guns forward for us, puts 'em behind you.
我会给你答案
I'll get you an answer.
有些具体细节需要敲定
Have a few more details to lock down.
然后我会告诉你全部计划
Then I can bring you all up to speed.
嗯 好的
Yeah, okay.
怎样 Clay的事情怎么办？
So what, what do we do about Clay?
我认为我们没有其他的选择
I don't think we have much of a choice.
我们也没有时间慢慢商议了
We don't have time to take it to the table.
如果我们不想这么做
If we don't want to do this,
我们就必须找其他愿意干的人
we gotta find somebody who will.
我打电话回堂口 让他们投票
I'll call TM, get the vote.
Jax Gaalan确实很疯狂 但他人很聪明
Jax, Gaalan, Gaalan's a
lunatic, but he's smart, man.
不管计划怎样
No matter what the plan is,
他们绝不会拿他们自己去冒险
they're not gonna put themselves at risk.
我知道 那样就更麻烦了
I know.That's the problem.
爱尔兰被抓之前就会挂掉
Irish will die before they get caught.
是啊 要是这件事情出了差错
Aye. And if this shit goes sideways, they're
他们肯定会采取血腥手段突围出去
gonna blast a very bloody way out.
就差他妈的一点 我们就成功了
We're so damn close.
我可不想 我们退出枪支生意的最后努力
I don't want our last push out
因为死了一大帮子警察而泡汤
of guns to end in a pile of dead cops.
不会的 兄弟
It won't, brother.
是的 我知道 我知道
Yeah, I know, I know.
嗯哼 好的
Uh-huh. All right.
好的 哥们
All right, mate.
问过每位兄弟 他们都同意帮爱尔兰人一把
Talked with everyone, they're good with helping the Irish.
好吧 看来我们入伙了
Okay. Looks like we're in.
事情差不多就这么定了
Door's almost shut, brother.
行 行 不管哪个都可以
Yeah, yeah, e-either one would be good.
没有更快点的？好吧
Nothing sooner? Okay.
不 不 不 不行 是的
No, no, no, I can't. I did.
好 好 好 多谢 算了
Okay, okay, okay, thanks.Just forget it.
妈的
Shit!
我知道你在里面 Wendy
I know you're in there, Wendy.
嘿 怎么了？
Hey. What's going on?
我知道你把一切都告诉了Gemma
I know you told Gemma everything.
你觉得现在怎么办 嗯？
What do you think happens now, hmm?
对我们两个人来说
To both of us?
事情已经糟糕得不能再糟了
Can't be any worse than
anything that's already happened.
老天
Jesus Christ.
你又吸高了？
Are you high?
没有
No.
我只是想从另外的角度思考一下
I'm just trying to get on the other side of it now.
Jax....知道了一切
Jax... knows everything.
你知道这意味着什么？
Do you know what that means?
他会反对把Gemma踢出局
He'll have the claim against Gemma thrown out.
要是我进了监狱 Gemma将会获得孩子们的监护权
And she'll get custody of my boys if I go to jail.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
不
No.
你到底在想什么？
- What were you thinking?
没想什么
- I wasn't.
到底他妈的什么意思？
What the hell does that mean?
意思是说 要是我以前是一个称职的妈妈
It means, Tara, if I were capable of being
我就不会同意帮你
a mother, I never would've agreed to help you.
因为这根本就是个错误
Because it was wrong.
是啊 你的事后诸葛亮这会儿没有用
Yeah, well, your Hazleton
hindsight doesn't help me right now!
是啊 谢你了 我 我知道
Yeah. Thanks. I-I get it.
听着 我不想再吸了
Look, I don't wanna use again.
我..我真是想戒掉 重新过上清醒的生活
I-I'm just trying to get myself into a
sober living or a rehab or anything.
上帝啊 Tara 你也得清醒一下
God, Tara, you gotta come clean.
和Jax谈谈 和Gemma谈谈
Just talk to Jax,talk to Gemma.
他们已经知道真相了
They already know the truth.
他们不知道你的真相
They don't know your truth.
告诉他们为什么你要这样做
Tell them why you really did this.
让他们知道你心里的苦楚
Let them see the pain that you've been in.
然后怎样？乞求他们的原谅
And then what? Beg them for forgiveness?
不 别再欺骗了
No. Just stop lying.
这才是正确做法
It's the right thing.
我做的一切 都是正当的
Everything I did was right.
Tara 对不起
Tara, I'm sorry.
你能闭嘴吗？你并没有感觉到对不起
Will you stop it?!You are not sorry!
知道为什么 你不是一个称职的母亲吗？
Do you know why you're not capable of being a mother?
因为你是个胆小鬼
Because you're a coward!
我不怕他们 再也不怕了
I'm not afraid of them. Not anymore.
你这什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
意思是 你是个愚蠢而软弱的瘾君子
Means you're a stupid, weak junkie.
糟糕
Shit!
这个疯婆娘
Crazy bitch!
Jimmy.
别来无恙啊 兄弟
How are you, man?
噢 还行
Ah, we're okay.
只是在一边看着你们演出可不太爽
Not too thrilled about having to put on a gun and pony show.
我知道
I know.
但是我也得为我们帮会多做打算 Jax
But I got a lot of years sitting around my table, too, Jax.
你还没出生 Aldo就认识了老林
Aldo's known old man Lin since before you were born.
我必须坦诚的说明这点 和Herry还有他叔叔谈谈
I gotta honor that, talk to Henry and his uncle
至少听听他们要说点什么
at least hear what they gotta say.
爱尔兰人？
Irish?
是的
Yeah.
是的 他们也想与会
Yeah, they wanted to be here.
以示敬意
Show respect.
Cacuzza先生
Mr. Cacuzza.
这位是Gaalan O'Shay还有这位Connor Malone
Gaalan O'Shay,Connor Malone.
幸会
- Pleasure.
先生们
- Gentlemen.
为了推销生意 我们打过几次交道了
Made quite a commute for the sales call.
我们认为值得和你们做生意
We think your business is worth it.
哇哦 早知道我们应该多打交道
Wow. I should do this more often.
你们很看得起我
You guys are great for my esteem.
带了什么好东西？
What do we got?
你知道的 克洛格全自动手枪
Handguns you know, Glocks are full auto.
带有扩展弹夹
Got the extended clips.
Ak冲锋枪是俄国原装存货
AK's are original Russian stock.
完全升级版 全新设计 上膛迅速
Fully updated, new action, quick load.
军用枪柄？
- Military handles?
是的
- Aye.
能吸收50%的后坐力
Absorb 50% more recoil.
这是全新的艾尔肯瞄准镜
It's the new ElCan scope.
喂 Jax 中国佬来了
Yo, Jax, Chinese.
试试这瞄准镜 它能够在3个街区外撕烂新教徒的一根头发
Try the scope. It can split a
Protestant hair from three blocks away.
耶 你真是个天主教的好孩子
Ah, a good Catholic boy.
嗯 感觉真不错
Yeah, that feels good.
打在人身上效果更好
They work even better on flesh.
把枪放下 放下
Put it down! Down!
Chibs 别
Chibs, don't!
走 走 走
Go! Go! Go!
快点走 走
走 走 走
Go, go, go!
他妈的搞什么？
What the hell was that?!
我就是要让你知道
That was just me letting you know
我们是多么看重和你们的生意
how much we want your business, Jimmy.
抱歉这种血腥的场面 但是发出这种强烈的信号很有必要
Apologies for the blood, but a strong message was needed.
我确信 你能理解这种重要性
I'm sure you can understand the importance of that.
嗯 这种信号是什么？
Mm. What message was that?
在北加州这块地盘上 我们是唯一的武器供应商 林清楚这点
We're the only source for guns
in Northern California. Lin knew that.
这可是破坏了 我们所推崇的自由贸易的规则
That kinda undermines the free market
strategy that we were attempting here.
我们能提供更好的武器 更优惠的价格
We've better guns, better price.
你知道会发生这样的事吗？
Did you know this was going down?
不 这不是我和你谈生意的计划 Jimmy
No. This wasn't the way I
planned to get your business, Jimmy.
现在就给你两折的价格
You've been paying 20% above cost.
明年Clay接手后 可以降到1折
I'll drop it to ten for the next year
while Clay makes the transition.
完了以后 最多1.8折
After that, it tops out at the 18%
这会让我们的一些人感到很不安
This is gonna upset some of my people.
1折18个月怎样
10% for 18 months.
完了以后变成1.5折
Then it jumps to 15.
两年至少1折 以后1.2折
Two years at 10%, then it jumps to 12.
行 我们成交吗？
Fair enough. Do we have a deal?
是的 我认为我可以让所有人都理解
Yeah. I think I can make everyone understand.
太好了
Excellent.
把尸体扔到车上
- Throw the body in the car.
我们去办
- We'll get it.
和你们的人讨论过新的安排吗？
Did you discuss the new arrangements with your table?
是的 我们同意参加
Yeah. We're good with that.
但是这单破事
But this shit?
这可是个麻烦
This is a complication.
不 不是的
No, it's not.
先生们 合作愉快
Gentlemen, been a pleasure.
我也没有料到
I didn't know this was coming.
抱歉
Sorry.
你的拍档很会谈生意
Your partner knows how to close a sale.
是啊 我很抱歉
Yeah. I'm sorry.
现在你知道我为什么要退出了
Now you know why we're getting out.
别担心 孩子
Don't sweat it, kid.
我永远都不会和中国佬交心的
I was never gonna go with the chinks.
想办法联络林或者那个那个老头
Try to get ahold of Lin or the old man.
我们必须摆脱这个干系
We need to clean this shit up.
相信我 我会搞定
Trust me, I'm on it.
这可没办法让林相信 不是我们设计好的
There's no way Lin's gonna believe we didn't plan this.
我们把中国佬惹火了 奥克兰州那边就会有麻烦了
We burn the Chinese, things are gonna jump off in Oakland.
那会怎样？
Then what happens?
那么我们将失去江湖平衡
Then we lose the balance.
我刚接到Wendy的电话
I just got a call from Wendy.
Tara去过她那
Tara went to her place.
嗯 似乎非常恼火
Uh, very pissed off.
说她想搞清楚一些事情
Said she seemed unraveled.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
我也不清楚 我让Rat把Juice和他的车接回来
I don't know, but we just sent
Rat to pick up Juice and his bike.
Tara把他的车给撞了 摆脱他的跟踪
Tara backed over him to the lose the tail.
该死
Damn.
孩子们在哪？
Where are the boys?
他们还在日托所里
They're still in day care.
Juice没事吧
Juice okay?
嗯 他也很恼火
Yeah, he's just pissed.
好吧 告诉Rat 把Juice送到圣托马斯医院
All right, tell Rat to take Juice down to St. Thomas.
看好孩子们
Keep an eye on those boys.
是的
Yeah.
嗯 我想还是我去照看Tara比较合适
Uh, I think I better be the one to go look for Tara.
我认为你最好去看看Wendy
I think you should check on Wendy.
听上去她不太好
She didn't sound so good.
又吸高了？
High?
呃 是病了
Uh, sick.
不 你去看看Wendy 我得去探望Clay
No, you got to go check on Wendy.I got to go see Clay.
我们拿Tara怎么办？
What do we do about Tara?
让她自己想清楚
Let her unravel.
也许我该和你一起去 和Wendy谈谈
Maybe I should go with you, talk to Wendy.
用瘾君子的方式谈
Junkie to junkie.
好吧 要是你想的话
Yeah, if you want.
我来开车
I'll drive.
开那部车？
In that?
来吧 Wayne 我让你感受一下地道的西班牙风格
Come on, Wayne, I'll get you
in touch with your inner cholo.
那我宁愿割掉我内脏
I had that removed with my spleen.
这只是个癌症的小玩笑
It's a little cancer humor.
好吧
Right.
我打电话给Rat
I'll call Rat.
打起精神....
Just a heads up...
他只是有点爱我
he's kind of in love with me.
开心点
Have fun.
我不知道有人在
I didn't know anyone was here.
你想要干嘛？
What do you want?
顺便路过 拿些孩子们的东西
Coming by to get some of the boys' things.
要是他们到奶奶家过一段时间 也许能用上
Just in case they need to spend some time at Grandma's.
是吧 那是不可能的
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
真的吗？
Really?
那你认为会怎样 Tara？
And what is it you think is going to happen, Tara?
你知道为什么你那么讨厌我所做的一切
You know why you hate what I did so much?
因为这些事情你应该做到的
Because it's something you would've done.
你一直是我的师傅 Gemma
You've been my teacher, Gemma, my...
我的教练 自从我回到Charming镇以后
old lady coach since I came back to Charming.
虽然你并不为我感到骄傲
Thought you would've been proud of me.
想方设法保护家人
Pushing the envelope to protect my family.
是啊 为了保护家人 我做过很多事情
Yeah, there's a lot of things I'd do to protect my family.
伪造孩子的死亡--可不包括在内
Faking the death of a baby--that ain't one of them.
看来是我把你看走眼了
Guess I misjudged you.
没想到你也有底线
I didn't realize you had a
line that couldn't be crossed.
似乎你把所有人都看走眼了 亲爱的
Seems you misjudged everyone, darling.
这就是为什么 你现在成为孤家寡人
That's why you're all alone.
从我家滚出去
Get out of my house.
如果不呢？
Or what?
你要把我赶出去吗？
You gonna run me over?
你无路可走了 孩子他妈
Your bridges are all burning, Mom.
我认为你最好多交点朋友
I'd think you'd be trying to make as many friends as possible.
我不需要朋友 我有我的家人
I don't need friends. I have my family.
你真的相信这个 对吗？
You honestly believe that, don't you?
你是怎么想的 这样做能成功？
How'd you think this was gonna play out?
假如发生最好的情形 你的计划成功了
Best case scenario,your plan worked.
你和Jax离婚 不管是你还是Wendy 把孩子带到
You divorce Jax, either you or
Wendy take those boys on up to
俄勒冈州或其他什么地方
Oregon or wherever.
你真的以为Jax会让这一切发生吗？
Did you really think Jax was gonna let that happen?
他别无选择
He'd have no choice.
你有没有想过你老公是何许人物？想过他的能量吗？
Do you have any idea who
your husband is? What he's capable of?
我远比你更了解他
I know him better than you do.
哦 不
Oh, no.
很显然你并不了解
Clearly you don't.
我儿子爱得越深...恨得也越深
My son loves deep...hates deeper.
这是遗传了我的基因
It's in our genes.
背叛是不可原谅的
Betrayal is unforgivable.
你所作所为 还有你打算做的
What you did, what you were planning to do--
都已经无可挽回
there's no coming back from that.
现在你能做的 只有告诉她 你很后悔 然后自己滚蛋
All you can do now is tell him you're sorry and go away.
我绝不会这样做
I'll never do that.
我绝不放弃我的孩子
Not without my sons.
你要听我这个建议 Tara
You need to hear this, Tara.
并且要完完全全听明白
And understand it on every level.
Thomas和Abel不会交给你抚养
Thomas and Abel will not be raised by you.
你现在要做的 只是决定要我们怎样告诉他们
What you do now will determine how we deliver that message.
要不就是 妈妈离家出走了....
Mommy moved away...
或者妈妈去世了
or Mommy passed away.
由你决定
Your call.
林和他叔叔都联络不上
Couldn't connect with Lin or the uncle.
打给餐厅 打给仓库
Tried the restaurant,the warehouse.
都没消息
Nothing.
好吧
Okay.
我要确保明天的行动
Well, I'm gonna make sure that
tomorrow's job doesn't end up in
不会因为与200个警察交火而上“44分钟”特别新闻
a 44-minute gunfight with 200 sheriffs.
你认为这次怎样才能脱身 哥们？
How do you think this one plays out, brother?
我也没主意 兄弟
I don't know, man.
要是所有人都指望你的能力 就很难置身事外
It's hard to unplug when everybody
depends on you for the power.
哪位？
Yes?
Jax电话找你
I have Jax Teller on the line.
把它接进来
Put him through.
二线
Line two.
Teller先生 有何贵干？
Mr. Teller, how can I help you?
今天我们拿到了Diosa Del Sur的执照
We got our license for Diosa Del Sur today.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气 现在该轮到你交货了
You're welcome. Now it's your turn to deliver.
我将在48小时之内 把Gaalan交给你
I'll give you Gaalan O'Shay within the next 48 hours.
能说详细一点吗？
Can you be a little more specific?
明天我去找你 把所有细节都告诉你
I'll meet you tomorrow, give you all the details.
你那边进行得怎样？
Can you prove your end?
我为你和你们的俱乐部起草了一份豁免协议
I've drafted an immunity deal for you and the club.
让我的手下为Tara做了一份认罪协议
Had my team set up a plea agreement for Tara.
会有一些罚金 还有社区服务作为处罚 但是不会进监狱
There's some fines, community service, but no jail time.
很好
Good.
Gaalan的手下是一些胆大包天 全副武装的家伙
Gaalan will have a large, well-armed crew.
你们需要很多人手 越多越好
You're gonna need manpower and lots of it.
明天我将告诉你什么时间 什么地点
I'll tell you where and when to send them tomorrow.
你认为她会上钩吗？
Think she'll take the bait?
这要看诱饵是什么
Depends what it is.
好吧 老大 去哪？
Okay, boss, where to?
Colette那
Colette's.
那么说 呃..从小你就认识Gemma 是吧？
So, uh... you know Gemma
since she was, like, a kid, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
那时就和现在一样疯狂吗？
She as crazy then as she is now?
我想差不多
I guess.
Jax的前妻 这个 呃 Wendy..
Jax's ex, this, uh, Wendy...
她戒了一段时间还是...？
sh-she been clean for a while or...?
是的
Yeah.
她在Charming镇长大的？
She grow up here in Charming?
不是
No.
我猜想是癌症把你一部分脑子腐蚀掉了
So I guess the cancer's eaten away that part of your
使得你连聊天都不会了
brain that can actually hold a conversation.
不 是把我对于那些不在乎的人的耐心给腐蚀掉了
No, it's eaten away at my patience
for people I don't give a shit about.
按我以前的做法 要是有人这样和我说话 通常我会
For the record, someone talks to me that way, I usually
把他的从车里拖出来 请他吃一顿好果子
grab their ass out of the car and
throw them an appropriate beat-down.
那是因为我的病让你原谅我咯
Guess I'm getting a pardon on account of my sickness.
喂 瞧 我死过两次 我被人砍过三次
Hey, look, I've been dead twice,
I've been cut open three times.
我还有个孩子得了脊裂瘫痪症 可能活不过15岁
I got a kid with spina bifida,
probably won't make it till he's 15.
所以说你的癌症 对我来说狗屁都不算 老兄
So your cancer, it don't mean shit to me, man.
我之所以努力搞好关系 是因为我知道Gemma
I'm trying to make an effort here because I know how much
很在乎你
Gemma loves you.
相信我 我明白得了那个病是多么艰难
Trust me, I know how hard it is to earn that.
谢谢你让我感觉糟透了
Thanks for making me feel like shit.
不客气 福尔摩斯大侦探
No problem, holmes.
小心左边
Left side!
开出去
Jump off!
妈的
Shit!
Jax 没事吧？
Jax! Are you okay?
把他扶起来
Pick him up!
你后面
Behind you.
糟了
Shit!
Jackie...
把枪放下 把枪放下
Put 'em down. Put 'em down.
好了 好了
All right, all right.
好了
All right.
我也没办法控制Gaalan的所作所为
We got no control over what Gaalan does!
那个神经病把我们两个弟兄砍成碎块 还把我们该死的堂口炸了个稀巴烂
Psycho just cut two of my guys into
pieces and blew up our goddamn clubhouse!
我们还和Henry与毒品集团一起做生意
We got the cartebusiness with Henry.
凭什么我会让爱尔兰人把他除掉？
Why would we okay the Irish to take him out?
冷静
Relax.
我如果要你们死 你们已经死了6次了
If I wanted you dead, I could've
killed you six times already.
那他妈的你想要干嘛？
Well, what the hell do you want?
你们要退出枪支生意
You're getting out of the guns.
我们却需要
We should have that business.
和毒品集团的生意渐渐清淡了
The cartel shipments have been grinding to a halt.
我需要道上的生意 这是我们的地盘
We need the street.This is our territory.
这是我们应得的
We own it, we deserve it.
没这么简单 先生
It's not that simple, sir.
那你让我无话可说了 小伙子
Then let me dumb it down for you, son.
你们当中任何一位 要想从这里离开
The only way any of you walk away from here is if you shut
就必须截断爱尔兰人的销售渠道 让我们的家族
down the Irish pipeline and my family take control over the
控制北加州的枪支生意
guns in Northern Californ.
我想我也没得选择 是吧？
I guess I don't really have a choice, do I?
是的，你没得选
No, you don't.
当你告诉我哪里能找到Gaalan先生和他的军火
And you close the deal when you tell me where I can find
事情才算完
Mr. Gaalan O'Shay and their guns.
我要他们为今天的所作所为付出代价
I need to even the score after what they did today.
Gaalan有一票货明天就到
Gaalan's got a shipment coming in tomorrow.
在一个新的地点卸货
Drop is at a new location.
当时候我会把时间和地点通知给你
I'll let you know when and where.
好的
Okay.
但是我要扣下你们其中一个 一直到交易结束
But I'll entertain one of your men until then.
以保证大家履行诺言
Keep everyone honest.
我喜欢这个看上去很疯狂的家伙
I like the crazy-looking one.
把你的爪子拿开
Get your hands off me!
我不会让你把我的人带走
I'm not letting you take one of my guys.
那我就把你留下
Then I keep you.
那也不行
Ain't happening!
不 你不可以
No, you're not!
我没事 老大
I'm cool, boss.
你们赶紧离开
You guys split.
我和老王走一趟
I'll chill with old Wang Chung.
说定了 明天
Tomorrow.
你在这干嘛？
What are you doing here?
有人把我撞倒 我总是要来医院吧
I always come to a hospital when someone runs me over.
告诉Jax 我不需要看门狗
Tell Jax I don't need a watchdog.
我只是负责看着Abel和Thomas
I'm just keeping an eye on Abel and Thomas.
确保他们不会去 他们不该去的地方
To make sure they don't go anywhere they're not supposed to.
这是老妈的命令
A request of their grandmother.
他在哪？
Where is he?
我不知道
I don't know.
你只要告诉我 他在哪 混蛋
Just tell me where he is, asshole.
Stockton的Diosa三陪会所
Diosa. Stockton.
和他的拍档Colette会面
Meeting with his partner Colette.
来 给你地址
Here. Let me get you the address.
她的车停在那
That's her car down there.
Wendy 你在里面吗？我是Wayne
Wendy! You in there? It's Wayne.
有股烟味 老兄
That's smoke, man.
哦 糟了
Oh, shit.
从里面传出来的
It's coming from inside.
嘿 Wendy
Hey, Wendy!
退后 退后
Step back, step back.
不 踢这....就踢这 这儿
No, kick it... kick right there, there right.
好的
All right.
嘿
Hey.
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit.
这里
Over here.
嘿
Hey!
这里
Over here.
她还有呼吸 我们得帮帮她
She's breathing. We gotta help her.
把他抬起来
Get her up there.
好了 来吧 起来
All right, come on.Come on.
来吧 我们走 快点
Come on,let's go, come on.
糟糕
Shit.
坐下 坐下 坐下
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
嘿 Wendy
Hey. Wendy.
醒醒 嘿 孩子
Come on. Hey, kid.
醒醒 快醒醒
Wake up, come on.
那可不是一般的烟雾 老兄
It ain't the smoke, man.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
这是新的伤口
Those are fresh.
哦 糟了
Oh, shit.
嘿
Hey.
很庆幸你能来
I'm glad you were here.
这会儿别拍马屁了
Don't suck up to me now, homes.
这让我很尴尬
It's, like, embarrassing.
这么仓促的叫你过来 太感谢了
Appreciate you making the trip, such short notice.
嗯
Yeah.
什么事？
What's this?
我让律师起草了一份文件
I had my lawyer draft something up quick.
是一份意向书
It's a letter of intent.
把财产都转移给你
Turning over assets to you.
修理厂的一半产权、房子、车 还有存在银行的东西
My half of TM, house, bikes, whatever I got left in the bank.
你为什么现在做这个？
Why you doing this?
因为 如果我逃跑 就不能申请离婚了
Well, 'cause when I drop out, I won't be able to
你懂的
file for divorce, you know?
现在把就所有的东西给你 就不会有麻烦了
This gives you everything without all the hassle.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
都安排好了吗？
That all set?
你的逃跑计划
Your drop out?
我们正在准备
We're working on it.
好吧 我....我希望你能得偿所愿
Well, I... I hope that all turns out the way you want it.
是的 当然会
Yeah, I'm sure it will.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们到另一头再见
See you on the other side.
是啊
Yeah.
好忙啊
It's busy.
生意谈妥了？
Business handled?
暂时吧 这里的情况怎样？
For now. How's things going here?
很好 都搞定了
Good. We're all set.
我打算明天和Lyla谈谈
I'm going to sit down with Lyla tomorrow.
争取赶上计划
Come up with a schedule.
很不错啊
That's great.
是的
Yes, it is.
大家随意 先生们
Make yourselves at home, gentlemen.
去吧 大家放松放松 明天才是关键
Go on, unwind. Tomorrow's a big one.
来吧 该你放松放松了
Come on.Time for you to unwind.
嘿 看来她打算自己戒毒
Hey. Looks like she was trying to get herself in rehab.
Wayne 帮他打包
Wayne, pack her a bag.
让她去哪？
Where's she going?
戒毒所啊
Rehab.
那间叫“要是你再吸 我就把你的奶子扯掉”的戒毒所
The If You Use Again I'll Rip Your Tits Off rehab.
我喜欢那家
I love that place.
来帮我一把
Come help me.
喂
Hello...
来吧 宝贝
Come on, babe.
嘿....我们去哪？
Hey... but where are we going?
回家 宝贝
Home, sweetheart.
嘿 需要帮忙吗？
Hi. Can I help you?
呃....是的
Um... yeah.
我找人
I'm looking for somebody.
没问题 她叫什么名字？
Sure. What's her name?
哦 不是....
Oh, it's not a...
嗯...哦 Colette
um... uh, Colette.
知道吗？这会儿 她在楼上和客人在一起
You know what? She's upstairs with a client right now.
如果你愿意稍坐一会 她一完事我就告诉你
But if you want to have a seat and relax,
I'll let you know as soon as she's done.
多谢
Thanks.
没事
Yeah.
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
Tara! Tara!
疯狂的....婆娘
Crazy... bitch!
Tara!
放开
Get off!
你这头蠢货
You stupid piece of shit!
放开我
Get off of me!
去吧 这儿有我
Go. I got this.
好吧
Yeah.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
那家伙是谁？
Who the hell was that?
他老婆
The wife.
Tara!
Hey! Tara!
不 你...
No, you...
你干什么...
What are you...
离我远点
Stay away from me!
你拿那个干什么？
What are you doing with that?
看你对我干的好事
Look what you did to me.
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
我到底怎么了？
What's happening to me?
What happened to me?
听上去很紧急 Knowles大夫
It sounded very urgent, Dr. Knowles.
是的
It is.
谢谢
Thank you.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
是的 我没事
No. I'm not.
我准备谈谈
I'm ready to talk.
有请...
Please...
谈什么？
About what?
我要谈交易
I want your deal.
你处在危险境地吗？
Are you in danger?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我只想照看好我的孩子
I just want to take care of my boys.
我要他们也列入证人保护计划
I want them in witness protection.
我很遗憾
Well, I'm sorry.
那个交易已经不存在了
That deal's no longer on the table.
请不要这样对我
Please don't punish me.
我没有带律师来
I'm here without a lawyer.
我可以给你任何你想要的
I'll give you whatever you need.
不是关于我的事情
This isn't about me.
我明白
I can see that.
只是眼下 我不能和你做这笔交易
I just can't offer that deal at this time.
还有其他的事要解决
There are other things pending.
要是你担心你和你孩子们的安全 我可以帮忙
If you fear for the safety of you and your boys, I can help.
不 你不能
No, you can't.
没人能帮到我
Nobody can help me.
Knowles 大夫
Dr. Knowles.
Tara!
原创翻译 倾情奉献
英语字幕：n17t01 翻译：Wilsonyy 校对：Dena